[Music playing]
Let me go!
Send him cheesy movies, the worst we can find.
He'll have to sit and watch them all,
and we'll monitor his mind.
Now keep in mind Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end.
He'll try to keep his sanity with the help of his robot
friends.
Robot rules called Kebab.
[Music playing]
If you're wondering how he eats and breathes
and other science facts, just repeat to yourself.
It's just a show.
I should really just relax for Mystery Science Theater 3000.
[Music playing]
OK, Crow.
This is a really, really big deal.
You know, your actions could change our lives forever.
Oh, Mike, that is it.
You are a miracle worker, young man.
Hi, everyone.
We're about to send Crow here on a highly confidential commando
raid down to Deep 13.
He's going to try to find the secret button that'll
get the satellite of love back down to Earth.
He'll be shot down the umbilicus at about 700 miles per second,
per second.
Oh, it's going to get real hot about halfway down, Crow.
Well, that's why we're greasing him up.
I thought it was because we liked him a whole lot.
OK, Crow.
Ingratiate yourself to these men.
Dr. Clayton Forrester.
Television's Frank.
Jeff Dunham and Peanut.
What?
Well, I had the head shot.
Less talk, more grease.
Right, got it.
You do see him down there.
He's got this old man that he does.
It's really funny.
[Music playing]
Oh, Crow, I can't believe you're leading
on this dangerous mission and you're not coming back.
Well, actually, I am coming back, Jimsy.
But Tom said you'd probably be caught and tortured.
Yeah.
Oh, goodbye.
Oh, wait, what did he say?
What did you tell her?
I told her the truth, that you are a brave and profoundly
stupid robot.
Oh, well, thank you.
Hey!
What it all comes down to, Crow, all those months of training.
We just thought of it this morning.
Goodbye, Crow T. Robot.
If we meet again, then we'll smile.
And if not, then this parting was well made.
Goodbye, my friend.
Oh, Tom, you big--
Ah, don't you hug me.
You're greasy and gross and I'll get a--
Hey, Crow, well, you got everything, buddy?
Yeah, I think so, Mike.
Oh, could you give me a hand with that?
Oh, sure.
Crow, this isn't a cyanide tablet, is it?
No, it's a vellament.
I had tahini for lunch.
For crying out loud.
Well, we better get going.
All right, telly ho.
Here we go.
Oh, oh, yeah.
This is where that bleach is really paying off.
Oh, you're going to think this is funny, but I left my--
[muffled screaming]
Fire in the hole!
[screaming]
Wha-- ha.
Jimmy jumpsuit.
This is Hermes.
The squab is in the hole.
OK, first impression.
Very dark.
[sniffing]
Very smelly.
Oh, wait, that's me.
Making preliminary search of area.
Hmm, nice.
Wonder what they pay for rent.
Crow, would you just find the secret button and get us down?
Right, sorry.
The golden bird is circling.
The eagle is ready to dive.
I'm just going to make it--
Hey, don't just stand there, pal.
Help me find the special button that gets the satellite of love
to-- la, la, la--
[laughing]
The eagle is running!
The eagle is wetting his pants!
Whoa!
[screaming]
Ow!
Frank?
Yes, sir?
Ah, put a nut rages in this and set it
at the bottom of the umbiliport, will you?
Okay.
[laughing]
I warned you, Nelson.
You keep your little robot pals where they belong,
or you're going to find a little surprise waiting for them.
Oh, yes.
[laughing]
Well, you can't blame a guy for trying.
Hush, little baby, don't say--
You can not only blame him, you can send him the experiment
kitten with a whip.
That rages!
Is that the one with the chocolatey nougat
sent you and the creamy caramel outside?
I don't know.
No, Frank.
Your experiment is kitten with a whip,
starring the very kittenish Ann-Margret
and the very whipped John Forsythe.
[screaming]
Say, this really is nut rages.
That's enough, okay.
You smell like rain.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, we got movie time!
[laughing]
You're better.
I know.
Yeah!
It's a swinging world, baby.
It's universal, so it covers everything.
Everything.
Whoo.
Oh, "Anatomy of a Murder."
Anyone else moiréing right now?
Oh, I just thought it was Ann-Margrock.
Twitch, Twitch!
Oh, it's the UPC code for this movie.
No.
Ooh, the hottest Garfield episode ever.
Puppy with a nunchuck.
Dick Dick with brass knuckles.
Yak with a Kentucky long rifle.
Hamster who writes a strong letter to the times.
[laughing]
With these guys.
Ha! With me.
Whoa, still good.
And those guys.
Ooh, I hope Doodle's Weaver isn't the kitten.
[humming]
[mumbling]
This is where the Pink Panther comes in.
You know, I think Jerry Lewis did a pantomime to this music.
You know, we had to...
All I have to do is loosen a few more bars
and we're out of the credits.
You know, Ann-Margrock can raise a few welts on me.
You need to have a telly if she's something else.
Oh, man.
Pow!
She is a kitten with a whip
and it hurts so good.
Dick Dick with a whip.
Yeah!
Pow!
Bam.
Come on, make with the kitten.
Kitten, come on.
Ooh.
Chucky.
Hey, we have our kitten.
The hills are alive.
Ann-Margret in the Woody Guthrie story.
I have a fusion from a slumber party.
Oh, man, how am I going to get to the hobo gathering?
Ann-Margret? I'm going for it.
Oh, ma'am, ma'am, you forgot your hot rollers.
Super city. You build it.
Ann-Margret, honey.
Please, no, I don't want to get dog hair all over my nightgown.
Ann-Margret?
Oh, she's going to go vandalize Mr. Ed's house.
Very interesting, but sexy.
She's standing on Donna Reed.
Ah, nobody reads The Voice anymore.
I just have to know if the twins lost again.
Convenient home delivery of Ann-Margret.
Hi, I'm Ann-Margret.
I'm selling candy to keep kids like me off the street.
Ethan Allen Galleries for great American homes like yours.
That's serious.
Ah, forget it then.
Cripes, how many hutches do they need?
And a salad bar.
Oh, with a decorative snot guard.
There's the lattice for the salad bar.
Boom. I bite you.
Mr. Letterman, darling.
Geez, what do we have here? Early American Danish Modern Colonial?
Oh, it's Michael Jackson's house.
Ah.
Teddy with a truncheon.
A little peek into Doodles Weaver's lifestyle.
Okay, we meet later and frag Sherry Lewis.
Russ Myers, Goldilocks.
I am one whipped kitten.
Lady, wait. I'm not ready for this.
I think we're moving too fast.
I don't even know you. I'm flattered, of course.
But the dear penthouse forum.
I am an average stuffed animal in a small midwestern college.
Okay, remain calm.
Well, thanks again. You sure you won't go in for a drink?
At this hour, why, Senator?
If I ever do become a Senator, Vera, I promise I won't be a clock watcher.
You promised me a preview of your speech for Friday, remember?
Oh!
Well, sit tight, man. I'll bring a copy out.
No, no, I need the exercise. I'll be just a minute, baby.
That's your usual limit for exercise.
Good night, Vera.
Good night, David.
Good night, Mr. Tutman.
We can rebuild you, John. You'll be faster, stronger.
Good night, David. You made a lot of friends.
Well, it's nice to be popular, but that's not my political objective.
I know, but you'll need all the friendship you can get within the party to cinch the nomination.
How about cinching my pants?
I told you. I make no commitments.
We're well aware of that, but, uh...
Can I offer you a hutch?
Are we alone?
The help's on vacation until Virginia gets back from San Francisco. Why?
Well, frankly, we hope she'll get back soon.
We'd like to see her on the platform with you when you speak next Friday.
Ah, yes, the public image.
Limited.
Well, I'd like that, too, but I can't guarantee it.
David, what's wrong?
I know she took Kathy up there to visit her grandmother, but was that the only reason?
Just the excuse. She needed time, Grant, to think things over.
Things?
Various what, nuts?
Oh, the things that build up over seven years of any marriage.
You can't lose yourself and your work without losing something else, too.
In my case, communication.
But we still want the same things.
Mainly...
Mainly we want the marriage.
You don't want to come to speech. It's not a political posture.
I happen to love my wife.
I know, and I'm not talking politics.
No, not entirely.
But they do get rough at this level, so, uh...
I like it rough.
Keep her by your side, huh?
I'll do what I can.
Not so hard. We still have lunch tomorrow.
Not so hard enough to skip a free one.
Probably at one o'clock, huh?
Yeah, we'll tee off at two.
Right. Good night.
Good night.
Yeah, tee off on this, Oscar Goldman.
It's the 20th hour of the telethon, ladies and gentlemen, and we're halfway to our goal.
Now to put on some pampers and watch Flower Drum Song.
Ah, good night, Ann.
Smells like Elvis in there.
Good to see the senator keeping up with the issues.
Sweeney Todd.
It's a very dangerous toothbrush.
Oh.
Hi, guy.
Oh, no.
We've got to find out more about this Russia thing.
Pookie Nuts is in trouble.
They made nasolabial troughs much bigger back then.
Did my fireplace make that noise?
Maybe my couch made that noise.
It could be the lamp.
Maybe my wife's portrait.
No, no.
We're about to see a political career come to a screeching halt.
Did Johnny Hodges let himself in?
Tong, did you meow?
No.
Oh, Ann, you dropped a stuffed animal.
This is going to be much better than pancakes.
This to me is the very definition of getting lucky.
No, no, don't.
What?
I waxed.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't doing anything.
I mean nothing wrong.
I didn't take anything.
I'm sure of it.
You must have the clearest conscience in San Diego to sleep like that.
Or were you sleeping?
Oh, I was pushed. Please don't get mad.
I already am.
Now before I pick up that phone, I want to know two things.
Who are you and who put you up to this?
And will you kiss me?
Put me up to it.
You need time on that, huh?
All right, start with the easy part, your name.
You do know your name.
Kitten W. Whip.
Jody?
Jody Drew?
Oh, I can't stay mad.
Well, that's why I call myself.
Very creative.
Another one you were born with.
Stanley Myron Handelman.
I don't use it, so why should you?
And besides, what's yours?
Oh, you wouldn't know.
You wouldn't know about the Stratton shipping lines.
That's right, mister.
I don't know a thing about you, and I don't know what you're trying to make of all this.
You're large, is that it?
You walk in your sleep.
You just happened to wake up in the wrong bed.
Or maybe you're expecting someone.
An indignant father, an outraged husband, a few photographers.
What if they get lost too?
I'm alone.
Is that what you think?
There's nobody else.
Oh, this is David Stratton.
Has Lieutenant Woodman come in yet?
He's with Mr. Carter, sir.
Let go of my ego.
I think Senator Kennedy might have handled this differently.
The VC kept coming.
I couldn't keep him off me.
No, don't do that.
Stop it.
I can see your roots.
It's no good.
It doesn't help.
I mean, it helps, but it's just not very convincing.
Right.
Right the first time.
I bet you're always right.
Go ahead and make your car.
I don't even care anymore.
Where is everybody?
Your wife, the little girl?
They're out of town.
But let's stick to your story.
Okay, I'm going to pack.
But it's all so silly.
And if my parents ever found out why they yanked me out of college on the spot,
well, they're terribly strict, terribly proper.
They'd never understand.
I mean, you know, these sorority initiates.
In the middle of summer.
Well, we're on a four-master system thing where they're thinking...
Let's call these terribly strict, terribly proper parents.
No.
No way.
Oh, is that it?
Trouble at home.
Yes, but will you listen?
If you'll tell it.
Alright.
Here's my pitch.
I'm a Martian with the CIA.
Like you said, I was running.
Running away.
Yeah.
I found your front door open a crack?
No, that's another lie.
Oh.
I set the one to screen next to the back door,
breaking and entering, 90 days next case.
Running from what, your parents?
Parents.
My parents were mangs.
I never knew who my old man was,
and I doubt if dear old mom does either.
No, it was Barney, Barney the slob.
One of her gentleman callers.
That's who I was running from.
Oh, I should have taken off years ago.
What happened last night?
I got to bed, but not to sleep.
Too much furniture falling down,
and too much of them doing the same.
See, they're acrobats.
I guess mother was taken unconscious.
She isn't too terribly strong.
Sorry, I put the emphasis on the wrong word there.
Then Barney stumbled into my room.
Baby bop too.
Looking for a live one.
What is this live one?
You follow all this?
You live behind walls here, man.
Where I come from is outer space.
Men are from Mars, women are from Venus, right?
Well, before I knew it, he was all over me,
but I got a knee up,
and it was almost worth it to hear him howl.
I made a die for the door, but he grabbed me.
I guess he would have killed me,
only I'm sort of slobbering myself.
I made it out the window.
I'm sorry, a little bit of the king slipped out there.
Man, how I got this far, I'll never know.
Perhaps it was your pert acting ability.
He did this.
Gave you a booster shot?
Oh.
You want to trade '90s or...
All I've been thinking about is the damage you might be doing me.
Well, that's not all I was thinking about.
I'm sorry.
You mean it?
You won't make me go back?
To that?
But you'll need help.
By the juvenile authorities.
We've met.
They'll either send me back or put me away.
Now, what's the difference?
That's the Jodie doll.
You wind her up and any way you point her, she turns up lousy.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
We'll think of something.
Oui?
Oui.
The Gestapo!
Oh, no, she's marking the couch.
Sure, fine, I'll get it.
I always have to get the damn door.
Well, good morning, Martha.
Oh, I hope I didn't get you off.
No, no, no, I was just...
Have you taken on the paper route?
Oh, these.
That's why I stopped.
They were scattered all over your front lawn.
Six days.
You know, the police say that's like an open invitation to burglars.
So here I am.
I heard that, yes.
I'll have to be more careful.
Working late and leaving early, coming and going through the garage.
I just never noticed them.
So bye now.
No harm done.
Okay, bye.
Well, what did you hear from my little sister?
Nothing.
Goodbye now.
Oh, she's fine.
Kathy's fine.
Everything's fine.
Fine, bye now.
I expect them back soon.
I'm not quite sure of the date.
Yeah, goodbye.
You'll be the first to know.
Bye.
Oh, David, I hope you don't think I'm checking up on you.
I just have to come by.
Oh, no, bye.
No, no, it was very considerate.
Okay, see you.
I'm sorry I'm not dressed.
Oh, I couldn't stay in any case.
Good, bye.
Unless there's something that...
I'll hold the fort or send up a flare.
Yeah, bye.
Okay.
Well, don't hesitate, dear, if there's anything at all.
Look, I've got a girl in the oven.
You do.
Thanks again.
Copper-bottomed old...
Goodbye.
Last night when you were running.
Was it sensuous?
You must have had some idea where you were going.
Mm, I've got this sort of aunt, you know, up in L.A.
Carpenter aunt lives in a trunk of wood.
She wanted to talk to my mother.
I guess she put me up all right.
Though I must admit, I like it better here.
Well, you can't stay here.
What am I...
Of course you can stay here.
You can't just leave.
Not like that.
How long have these been here?
Well, if I could borrow something,
I could mail it back for my aunts.
Maybe your wife's got some old thing she's ready to throw away.
Aside from me.
As long as I've known her, she's never thrown a thing away.
Anyway, she's not your size.
What size is she?
Seven.
This way, please.
Well, let me show you something
in the Ruth Buzzy line of leather and PVC.
These are the sevens.
Any particular color?
Oh, just something cool.
Transparent.
This one, maybe.
Mm, very nice.
I would go slip it up.
Practition two.
Drip dry.
Fine.
Needs no ironing.
Fine, I'll take it.
Whatever.
Fine.
I'll need some other things, too.
You know, some of those filthy things.
Might as well give me the mannequin, too.
Do you have the rest of your wife's measurements?
Yes.
Oh, your wife is hot.
But, David, I never thought I'd find you in ladies' underwear.
Hi, Peggy.
Don't worry, I'll keep your secret.
Ooh.
Ooh, Andy.
A surprise for Virginia?
Oh, David, a size seven, she'll never squeeze into that.
She's a tank.
I'm not sure that we have that dress in a larger size.
However...
It's all right.
If it doesn't fit, she can always exchange it.
Oh, David, believe me.
Oh, Peggy, please.
I'll admit I'm completely out of my element here.
All I want is to grab something and run.
How about me?
Oh, darling, of course.
No, no, it's lovely.
She'll love it.
That's what I'm smashing.
I'm sorry, I just remembered.
I've got to put a nickel in the parking meter.
I'll be back for these.
Nice to have seen you, Peggy.
You too.
Mistress.
[music playing]
It was all worth it.
Well, am I terrific?
That's the word.
Oh, David, everything's so creamy.
Oh, don't say that.
Oh, kill me quick.
I never had it so good.
Yeah.
What do I do?
I mean, just say thank you.
It just sounds so nothing.
That sounds fine to me.
When you need to come back, I'm scared you wouldn't.
What, and leave you my house?
But that's why I trusted you, because you trusted me.
And that's something I never did, not ever, not anyone.
But I feel so shiny good about you, about everything.
Like wonderful.
More clothes, got to put her more clothes.
Let's buy stuff for her.
Oh, David, I'm really flying.
Yeah, it's good stuff, isn't it?
New shoes, new everything.
Riding in a big new car.
With a big new you.
Well, now you can ride in a bigger one.
Here's the bus stop.
Say hello to the stinky guy.
It would be.
You're better untie me.
Well, I knew it couldn't last.
Nothing does.
You wouldn't want it to.
You've got things to do, places to go.
90s to wear.
This will get you started.
Today, Los Angeles, tomorrow, the world.
All right, but I'm keeping score.
You just tell me what you spent on me and someday you'll get it back.
I promise.
No, I mean it.
Someday I'll be rich and famous.
I'll be the prize, Paulette sir.
Then I'll do something for you.
I'll do something for somebody else.
It's all in the family.
What kind of crystal rubbing bull hockey is that?
So long, Jody.
Bye, Buffy.
This purse doesn't go with this outfit, pal.
Thanks, David.
Thanks for everything.
No, thank you.
Oh.
The steering wheel's about to snap in his hands.
There isn't the shower cold enough for this man.
[laughing]
Mike, what are you doing?
Yeah, you know, robot maintenance isn't exactly your strong suit, buddy.
Yeah, I know, but in honor of Oscar Goldman, who you might have noticed is in today's film,
I'm giving you really cool bionic man/bionic woman noises.
Huh.
Be all done there.
There you go.
So?
Well, come on, you have to, you know, move around a little bit
and you'll be enchanted and bemused by what you find.
Check it out.
See?
Ooh.
Wow.
For the first time in my life, I know what it must feel like to be Lee Majors.
Is that a good thing?
Here, let me try.
Hey, see?
Wow.
Let's go try jumping up and down.
It's great.
Okay.
Now let's do it together.
It's 1974 again.
This is great.
[singing]
Oh, it doesn't hurt because I'm bionic.
This is the best I've ever, huh?
This is great.
[singing]
I love my new bionic woman/biotic man song.
Okay, watch this.
Bring it in here.
This is getting a little -- parts of it aren't really that fun anymore.
Could be taken as being really sort of annoying.
All right, I'm going to turn you into shields and yarn now.
Now come here.
No, this is way too --
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Over here.
[singing]
My late, you were looking at your watch.
I was checking the watch, not you.
One o'clock is right, which means you're martini, very cold, very dry.
No olive, no twist.
We'll be here in exactly 30 seconds.
Can I get one before that?
Wasn't that predictable?
Correction for predictable, read precise, which reminds me of speech.
It's pretty slurry.
I like it very much.
But women already have a vote.
It might be a little too specific at this stage anyway.
You can afford a few generalities.
Now that's where we disagree, Grant.
I believe --
Whoa, meeting's over.
End of disagreement until after lunch anyway.
Here's to big-ass steaks.
Oh, by the way, Philip Varden's in town just for the weekend.
Taking him and his wife down to Tijuana for the highlight games tonight.
We're hoping that you could join us.
You know, his newspapers do have the largest combined circulation on the West Coast.
It might be fun as well as political.
It might be fun is good enough.
I've never met him.
Besides, I'd like to get away.
Good, you've been sticking too close to home with Virginia Gaughan.
His hair is pulled back into a severe bun.
Grant, I've got to tell you what happened to me.
Funniest thing.
Bunch of newspapers landed on my lawn.
Maybe not so funny.
Sort of sad maybe or poignant or hopeful.
Or erotic.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Oh, no.
I'm losing my buzz.
Andy, would you ask the bartender to turn the volume up on the television, please?
Right away, Mr. Stratton.
Susie, chapstick was arraigned today.
There's a thing on Fabio.
For 17-year-old Jody Devork, who broke out of juvenile hall last night
after setting fire to the girls' detention workers
and stabbing the matron who tried to stop her.
The matron, Mrs. Clara Eckert, 46, is described in critical condition.
Well, did you know that, girl?
Think brain.
Come on.
No, I thought I did.
This joyful scene was enacted today in San Diego
when Matthew and Howard O'Donnell, Agent 7 and 8...
She looked a little like...
Dee Snider.
What's-her-name?
You know.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah, a little around the eyes.
Like what's-her-name?
Ha ha, you're so stupid.
Well, anyway, about this terribly funny thing that happened to you,
I thought it wasn't funny at all.
Oh, Adam Sandler.
Oh, sad or poignant or...
Let's change the subject, shall we?
God, fine.
You think I'm voting for you, you're crazy as son of a...
Oh.
Please, God, make it happen again.
Maybe this time, Sue Lyon or Jory Heatherton.
Oh, please, please, please.
Oh, this car handle's much easier after three martinis.
Look out.
Hey, someone stole my banana-seat bike.
He's driving into the abyss.
Ah, yes, my lightly propped garage.
This is all from the steering wheel's point of view.
It's the beginning of his own sitcom.
He's home, yes, he's home.
Kyle Stallings in his house.
Hey, something good.
All right.
Who took these out of their plastic bags?
Oh, that's right, I rented the spare room to Elmer Fudd.
Jody?
You're supposed to stay out of my room.
Are you alone?
There's a rabbit boiling on the stove for you.
Hi.
I'm Ann-Margaret.
I was afraid you might bring someone home with you,
and here I am with my...
Jody, what in the hell...
Hands off, buster.
Whoa, big old mood swing.
Don't you ever booz me, David.
God knows what I might do to you if you ever booz me.
Did you ever read The Burning Bed?
Oh, be nice.
Don't be mad. What have I done to you?
Jody, there's a woman in the hospital
who may be dead by now because of you.
Oh, so that's it.
She tried to stop me. That was her mistake.
And coming back was yours.
David, listen.
Don't you even want to know why I came back?
I do know. The police are looking for you.
David, wait.
Look, I'm only a girl. I panic.
What if I'm caught? What if they work me over?
Don't you see? I'm thinking of you, how you helped me
and the way they could twist that.
David, if they work me over, it might come out real wild
and wrong.
Or even if they don't.
I told you I'd keep you out of it.
But I had it down my hair,
and I found it laid low a couple of days.
Here, of course.
Where else can I go?
Ann, move. Get out of here.
I want to see Sylvester.
Because you weren't running away from home or Barney.
You do remember Barney? Barney the slob?
He loves you. You love him.
That was the truth.
Only it didn't happen last night.
I was 15.
I am as sympathetic as sorry for you as I was this morning.
More so.
But you need a lot more help than I can give you.
You need Joel Hyatt.
I hope you understand. I'm going to telephone the police.
I'm going to tell them the truth,
and you can tell them anything you want.
Put it down!
I got two 38s pointed at you.
You poke your finger at that dal, mister,
and that's when I start screaming rape.
Huh?
It's not creamy anymore?
You're insane. Who'd believe you?
The police, your wife, every dirty little mind in town.
Oh, prince.
You don't think so?
A girl under 18, running scared, a fugitive?
But you take her in, sure.
You tuck her into bed, you give her money,
you buy her clothes.
For what?
Because he's so shiny, bright, and a big white hat?
Or because your dirty creep whose wife is out of town?
Not just a creep, but a sick creep.
That's how I'll tell it.
That's what started me screaming, because you're sick.
I feel like my world is about to blow up.
Well, go ahead, be a hero.
It might be fun.
I'll get my claws into you before anyone gets here.
We'll both be so torn up by then, I'll be hysterical.
You might even do me some good.
They'll pity me for a change.
I'll be a celebrity, and so will you.
Ah!
This is fun, and here's your old shipmate, Salty Sam,
to tell you all about a real fun game that you can play with grown-ups.
All you have to do is...
Well, go on, killer, throw the dice.
You turned off doodles, Weaver.
All right.
Okay, you win. I'm in love with you.
What is that noise?
Where have I heard that before?
(phone ringing)
Yes?
Yes, I saw it. I love doodles, Weaver.
Hello, Jenny.
It's my gin distributor.
No, no, no, I'm fine.
I don't know, I may be a little hoarse.
Who is it, your wife?
No, no, no, of course not.
When?
Yes, tomorrow?
Sunday, yes, 10 a.m.
What time?
I've got it.
I'll be there.
Squirt water at her.
Don't...
Dick Van Dyke show.
David, what was that?
It sounds as if the house is falling down.
Oh, honey, I took in a stray cat while you were gone.
Hello?
What's wrong with this connection?
Are you in?
Don't overplay it, Jody, or so help me.
You'll what?
I'll obey you like a slave.
Thank you.
No, now he has to keep her and get rabies shots.
[music]
Say, is Kathy there?
She's trying on a bathing suit and saying "ack" right now.
Oh, well, kiss her for me, will you?
And...
Yes, kiss her very hard and very deep,
and then slip her nightgown off her shoulder and commit.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Yes, I'll be waiting.
You know, Endora's never done anything for me.
Bye, Ginny.
Love you, too.
Maybe if I could just keep her in the backyard.
Well, tell me, Tiger, do I fill it out as good as Ginny?
Or maybe you notice something different like?
Take that off.
Put those drapes back.
My, oh, my.
When you do react, you really do.
In there, get your clothes on.
You're getting out of here.
Oh, no, I'm not dreaming.
Alrighty then.
You better change that shirt now
and do something about those scratches.
Iodine or, uh, no, here's something better.
A real germ killer.
Thank you.
Ha!
Now how much do you hate me, lover?
She's got her own sense of humor.
Is that what you want from me, hate?
But why?
I'm the same man who tried to help you this morning.
Accessing, accessing, reboot.
Shut down.
[humming]
Don't ask me why.
I can't help it.
I am one spooky chick.
Oh, I'm sorry, David.
I really am.
I thought you were someone else.
Hello?
I see something all bright and shiny.
How far can a metaphor be stretched before it snaps?
Right away I've got to pull it apart to see what makes it right.
Oh, maybe you could fix my toaster.
And then it never runs again.
And then you end up having to bring it into the shop anyway.
I'll go.
I'll get out.
Just, uh, give me a few minutes to comb my hair and clean up the mess.
You can't talk me out of this, so don't even try on that sheer black teddy.
What did I say that worked this time?
Uh, Anne, that's my stuff.
He'd never touch you, picture.
You're dirt.
Go on, smile.
You think you've got it so made.
[mumbling]
[knocking]
Are you ready?
Just a minute, David.
I still have to do her mascara.
Whoa, wrong face.
I got mixed up there.
I'm here for our wedding, right?
What's wrong?
Why aren't you dressed?
Like my hair?
Yes, yes, it's an improvement, but it's a disguise.
Does it make me look older?
What if I wore it up like this?
Fine, fine, either way.
Now, you've got to get your clothes on, and we have got to get out of--
Well, you're going to think I have an awful dirty mind, David.
I change it so often.
But I'm not going.
You are going, and now--
You need shots.
What's that again?
Oh, sweetie, lest we forget, I call the shots.
Unless you really do want to see your nasty old picture in the paper
next to poor little mine.
So we're back to that again.
Well, just so long as they spell my name right.
Don't take it so downy.
You know your trouble?
You waste an awful lot of time trying to make sense when nothing does.
Bookies and pushers make more than preachers.
They drop the bomb tomorrow, so I worry.
Who cares?
Bomb?
There's something to live by.
So join the living.
We're alone.
We have the whole house to ourselves.
You be daddy, I'll be mine.
I don't kiss mommy.
Expecting someone?
Good lord, I forgot.
Well, shall I let them in?
How we doing?
Get out of here.
It's the diaper service.
Open up.
We come very--
Oh, isn't that nice?
We can have a party.
We can show them your scratches.
All right, Jody.
All right, you win.
Now, get out of sight until I can get rid of it.
If I do, daddy, you promise to behave?
I don't know if I can trust you here alone with me.
You're so physical.
Let me hear your party talk.
Better wipe the lipstick off.
Good, thanks.
I'll tidy up down here.
It's probably the Senate Ethics Committee dropping by unannounced again.
Welcome home.
Oh, not for you, David, for Virginia.
Well, then you've heard.
I talked to her right after you did.
Come straight in, Carter.
Yes, ma'am.
That goes in the bedroom, Carter.
I'll take that.
Oh, don't you dare.
It's very clumsy and full of water, and besides, Carter has it balanced beautifully, haven't you, Carter?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, don't bother to nod here.
Let me lead you.
The poor dear can't see a thing.
That was just a little further on.
Shut up.
Now we have five steps up.
One.
Shut up.
Two.
Three.
Oh, my back.
Oh, God.
Five.
There we go.
Now, not too fast or you'll splash.
Good, Carter.
Good boy.
Now we're going to make a left turn.
In we go.
That's right.
Now a sharp right.
I bet you'll like Ann.
I hope you don't mind the floral invasion, Dave.
You're not allergic to flowers.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's just that-
Personally, I am.
I can't stand cut flowers.
Always put me in mind of funerals, but Vera-
No, it was very thoughtful, really.
Of course, we're both delighted about you and Virginia.
Yes.
Well, so am I.
What are you drinking?
Oh, just tonic for now.
Vardon doesn't drink at all, and though he has no objection to-
Vardon.
Vardon, yes.
We're going to pick him up.
Say, we're not too early.
We did say between six and seven.
Did we?
I thought we said-
Oh, Vera, did you find a place for him?
Then did you meet the maid?
Yes, but David, would you come here a moment, please?
Will you show Carter how to undo my bra?
Would you wait for us, Carter, please?
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, sure.
Carter, do this.
Carter, do that.
Carter, you're fired.
There's something I don't understand.
Is Colonel Sanders back from the dead or what?
That.
Oh, she was eating a Clark bar.
Have you had trouble with vandals?
It's been simply-
The crawling eye.
... in our neighborhood just over the hill.
What's the only way, Vera, you recognize the touch of an up and coming Grandma Moses, kindergarten
class?
Of course, Kathy.
He's trying on a bathing suit and saying, "Ah."
But honestly, it looked so weird.
Well, there have been so many odd occurrences.
I think I'll take gin with that tonic after all, David.
Yeah, booze, all right.
... satisfied.
Of course, you wouldn't have the heart to remove it.
Well, I'm leaving that for her to do, the little monster.
Well, I'm thinking of.
But I must say, I'm entitled to be a little traumatic by on the way over here just a few
minutes ago-
Now, Vera, that's my story.
On the way over here what?
We were stopped by the police, a roadblock.
And-
Who do you think they were looking for?
Vera, please, will you let me tell it my way?
Should I know?
That girl.
Marlo Thomas.
The one on television, the one who looks like-
Pinkus Zuckerman.
What's her name?
Right.
You're bloody well right.
Since it's just Oscar, I'll get the Fleischman's out.
Roadblock?
Uh-huh.
Apparently they set them up around the whole area.
There's the coast route, the inland route.
They can even cork off the back road so that all traffic have to funnel through.
Phoebe.
Phoebe Grotkop.
That's who she looks like.
She's got someone helping her, that's for sure.
The young Gladys Kravitz chronicles.
Yes, someone's behind her.
She had to have help.
She was in this prison nightgown.
She looks like pebbles.
David.
You have the Mark of the Beast on you.
Is there someone else in the house?
What?
No.
Your telephone.
I didn't hear it ring, but one of the buttons lit up.
Oh, I must have left the receiver up on one of the extensions.
Who are you?
Lovejoy?
Leave me alone.
Tsk, tsk, Mr. Forsythe.
No one on the line.
Isn't that odd?
I was practically positive.
I'll have a look.
David, there's some DNA samples on the rail and some carpet fibers on the road.
That better be a local call.
Have to get her own princess phone.
I bet she crawled away to have kittens.
Ah, she's calling Bob Woodward.
There, that should solve everything.
She'll leave now.
I'm going to get her.
That should solve everything.
She'll leave now.
Jen and I would like to announce our engagement.
She's in the bedroom.
Oh, I bet I know what happened.
Carter knocked it off the hook and he was fumbling around with the clockworts.
That's possible, yes.
But David, shouldn't you be putting on a jacket or something?
After all, we did promise the Barden.
Oh, well, that's something else.
I'm sorry, but I just can't get away tonight.
What's that?
I'm under house arrest.
This isn't just a social call.
Barden's support could assure you of the nomination.
I know, I know, he's very influential, but we'll have to make it another night.
I've developed this headache.
Oh, I have the remedy for that.
Three aspirin.
Not two, but three.
It's really fantastic.
I tried everything to get rid of it, but nothing works.
Maybe you should get out of the house.
It'll do you good.
No, that just may get worse.
I can't go.
What I'm trying to say is get out, get out, get out.
Was Virginia coming back first thing in the morning?
Of course, that is more important.
The Vardins will be disappointed, but they do plan on staying over till tomorrow.
Well, then, Virginia and I could both meet them.
Fine, I'll find out what their plans are.
It might work out even better.
Poor David, I'm so sorry.
You ought to get right into bed with that headache.
Don't worry, I'll take care of it.
Have fun, you two, and please extend my apologies.
Of course, I'll give you a call in the morning.
Good night, David.
Night.
Bye.
Oh, my God, Carter's back in my life.
Carter of the rainy afternoons.
Carter of the tears and scotch.
Carter of the foggy drive through London streets.
I gotta say, I miss my bionic sounds.
Yeah, they were so...
Hey, part of me still works.
Yeah, which part?
I'm not sure.
Oh, come on.
Now, look, something's coming in on the hexagon.
Hey, look at that little guy there.
Hey, howdy.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Oh, yeah, hi.
I'm the kitten with the whip, you know, with the...
Yeah, sure.
Like I was saying there, I'm the kitten with the whip,
and the...
Oh, I'm the kitten with the whip, and I was with...
Well, anyway, moving it to...
What are you doing?
Stop that.
Stop that right now.
Close the hexagon.
Oh, my God.
Oh, we got movies.
Thank goodness we got movies.
Oh, wow.
Oh, man.
Nurse Ratched.
She stole my cigars, too.
Okay, if you want me to.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
She's going to do the funny dance again.
Say, hi, boy.
You up for some tricks?
Saigon.
Can't believe I'm still in Saigon.
Oh, that's an interesting stain.
How'd that get there?
Cinnamon Crispano's.
Where can I get some Cinnamon Crispano's?
But I don't want to run with the ball.
No.
Hey, get your cheap Mexican crap.
Hey, blanket-y hat kind of stuff.
Goofy little carvings with a sort of Latino theme.
Hey.
Out of the way, skipper.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, little buddy.
Guy from the taco around here.
Hey, crap.
Move it, Padre.
Welcome to Coincidence Corner.
Well, $110 for a bottle of 7 Crown.
That seemed reasonable.
Oh, no, it's Imogene Coca.
David.
Dad.
Mom.
Laurence Olivier.
Mildred Natwick.
Oh, Grant.
You see, I made it after all.
I was looking for it.
See, my headache is better.
Oh, whoa, sorry.
You're filming a movie here.
We're sorry about that.
Terrible.
Your clothes.
What's happened?
I had an accident.
The car.
What?
Oh, nothing serious.
Isotope models.
Get your isotope models.
I'm David Stratton.
Urban Adams.
Oh, I am sorry.
The surprise I've seen.
Philip Vardon, Mrs. Vardon, may I present David Stratton.
How do you do?
You do.
I was looking forward to meeting you, young man.
Don't be stingy with the hooch old boy.
Not under such dramatic conditions.
How did it happen?
What?
The accident.
Oh, I hit a fence post.
No, how could you do that?
Well, it wasn't easy.
Where is the car, David?
See, that's where I'm headed right now, garage.
Oh, but David, we have Carter with us.
You know Carter.
He can fix anything mechanical.
You just tell him where the car is.
Oh, no, no, I found the man.
I don't want to be a senator any matter.
As a matter of fact, that's why I have this bottle.
That was his price.
You see, for leaving the corner bar.
That's a marvelous story.
Let me tell you about a time in India.
I took a poo-drop bullet and I--
Of course, my curiosity.
Yes, of course.
Well, I wasn't done.
You have to be more careful.
After all, we can't have our candidate
banging in the fence post.
I'm not a candidate yet.
However--
Jeez, it's Cuntinfloss.
It's awfully crowded here.
Let's go inside.
It's awfully crowded there, too.
We just came out.
Oh, then you've seen the forester.
Well, no.
Well, then you're in luck.
Just beginning.
Best in town.
Really, I recommend it.
Come on, you old war wagon.
I'm trying to get out of here.
Stacy Keach, all cleaned up.
He's smoking a Slim Jim.
Whoo!
Wow!
Amy Grant has really crossed over.
Oh, Jesus loves me.
This I know.
'Cause the Bible tells me so.
So my feeling is the campaign should be financed with small--
Hold on, she does this thing with quarters here.
It's great.
Anyway, by strengthening local government,
I believe we can--
Let me just stick a dollar in there.
It'll be right--
Whoo!
It's amateur night, my dear.
Fellow in my squadron used to do that.
Floor show.
Real Mexican culture.
Ho, ho, ho, ho.
Ice atoners.
Heh, heh, heh.
Program has changed since I was here last.
They used to have a flamenco group.
Oh, they had this girl.
I love flamenco.
All the native dances.
Yes, even the classical ballet is, uh--
Well, senior wats is like it.
His arm is okay.
He's healthier than you.
♪ Heart and soul of fellow ♪
Man, I love Chi-Chi.
Hey, dingo balls, sit down.
The mechanic.
I really can't keep him waiting.
Please don't get up.
It's been a pleasure.
Hey, little young man, I'll give you a kiss.
I'll see you in the morning.
Yeah, little young man, I'll give your campaign millions.
Oh, guys, this isn't the kind of place we want.
Where can we get a piece of pie?
Stratton!
Oh, great.
I'm ready to be your hostage again.
Oh, beautiful.
He shot me so full of stuff, I'm halfway off the pavement, yeah?
If that's what it takes to feel like this,
I might go in for self-inflicted wounds.
Oh, which reminds me, I, uh, I have a surprise for you.
You like gum?
You a razor?
Oh, then, uh, then you've seen Buck, huh?
I had some trouble getting him to part with that.
He's, he's in a nasty mood, you know?
I mean, I don't, I don't mind if he roughs her up with her,
you know, but, uh, I mean, you don't either, right?
She's got a covenant, right?
Hey.
But, uh, no more cutting, right?
So you just tell me where she is?
Who?
Oh, now, now, look, buddy, sir,
look, you can still keep out of this.
I mean, stay neutral, man.
Don't enlist.
You just tell me where she is, and I'll tell Buck.
Or would you rather tell Buck?
Officers, over here!
Huh?
Hey, it's Soper Pills.
They got Soper Pills.
Come on, man.
This young man's annoying me.
He keeps trying to sell me something.
Marijuana.
Hey, I want some.
Just a little for the weekend, that's all.
One of my ideas worked.
We will overtake him.
What he does is very much against our laws.
Number nine, we are standing still.
Every day I sit in here, Charlie gets stronger.
I anchor.
Yes.
Come in, it's open.
[laughs]
I'm not in the mood to drink anymore.
Could you give me a Diet Coke?
An opener.
Two.
Now the keys.
Wow, I did another thing right.
I hope you like Annie Greenspring.
[sniffles]
Maybe you'd better count them.
Okay.
One.
What's happened, Jody?
What's wrong?
Just go, you idiot.
Really?
The party's off, that's all.
I'm ready to party and you poop out.
Go on, David.
Forget it.
I'm fine.
I feel right at home here.
Well, she needs my help.
She's always been there for me.
Are you sure you'll be safe?
I ran into Ron.
He and Buck, they're out looking for you.
I gave them your address.
I know, I told you.
God, you are always way ahead of me.
No, they don't know this pad.
I'm safe.
Safe as I've ever been.
Thanks for caring.
The United Way.
But I'm gonna be all right.
I made up my mind.
I'm keeping my baby.
I've had it with places like this.
It's Motel 6 from now on.
And guys like Buck and Ron.
Buck and Ron on three.
[grunting]
But you've got, that's what I want.
When you done with it?
Serenity, security and all that jazz.
I still think bland is the way to go here.
And someday I'll have it.
Actually, it's not looking real good.
Someday you'll see me and you'll say,
Damn, there she is.
I said good looking woman.
You won't say it in that voice.
One with good looking kids.
Bugs seem alone.
You won't even know me.
Yeah, that's gonna happen, uh-huh.
[gibberish]
I won't say hello.
All right then, bull boy.
So long, David.
Take it easy.
You know, I had a pretty good time after all.
So long, Jody.
Few kids ever need another hostage.
Oh, hi guys. Look, Jody.
Gentlemen, callers.
Think we couldn't find that white bucket of yours?
In this jerk town?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
What was I thinking?
I have common sense.
Hello, Jody.
Just look what you did to me.
This is a single occupancy room.
Call the concierge.
You know where the door is.
You don't have to see this unless you get your kicks that way.
Get him out of here.
Yes, of course you're right.
Well, well.
So we choose up sides.
I'll take the big guy.
Fine.
You can have each other when I'm done.
That's thoughtful, thank you.
But you're gonna throw up when you see what's left.
Thanks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The cameraman must not have expected this.
Biff, bam, zach, pow.
Not since the who were here has this happened.
That's the taxophone building.
That's for gat and for nastle.
There's a nice montage.
Go right to your head, though.
You're gonna do what I say, Ron.
Oh, you're dead.
I'm just sitting here.
I'm getting him to a doctor.
An arm or no arm, you're gonna help me drag him to the car.
He's back all injured again.
Can I have my sombrero?
Now, don't make a big thing of it.
Oh, you went and made a big thing of it.
Hang on, David. We're almost there.
Oh, Blicky.
Certified new shot. We promise.
Do not recycle.
I don't know how we got this car, but let's get him.
Whoa, don't move. Back to the car.
Mexico would have a better retail environment if they employed signage.
Just cleaning out the spit valve.
Dizzy Gillespie's on their tail.
Now this movie's lost its creaminess.
Let me know if you get tired.
It's like Clash of the Bands.
Pow, pow, pow, pow, pow.
I'm hoping for appropriations, although as a freshman I have no power.
You have to understand how...
There, now they're gone.
Manics.
Hey, it's going over 50,000.
David, I'll get you to a hospital.
Back across the border through the big gates.
They won't follow us there.
You're the driver.
No, I think you're right. They've given up.
Did I tell you a niner did poly-side?
Hey, good luck. We'll be back to bump you off later.
Don't encourage them, honey. They're trying to get to you.
Hey, your lights are off.
This must take place in Alaska where the nights are six months long.
Oh.
Turn into the skid.
Oh, for...
I should have told you I'm transporting napalm to my aunt's house.
Yeah, this is close enough. I'll walk from here.
Viva Las Vegas...
Lucky Hill.
Please, God, I'm only 17.
Hello, sir. I am the devil. God of hellfire and all.
Mr. Stratton?
Yes.
The name's Enders.
You're gonna finish your pudding?
Yes, Mr. Enders.
Sergeant Enders.
You're wife's out in the hall with the doctor. Been here since morning.
They're getting pretty cozy.
This is Sunday night.
I guess you'd rather talk to her first.
No, just tell her I left.
No.
No, I'll... I'll talk to you first.
You're...
Sure you're up to it?
I don't know. How bad am I?
Well, you're in this movie.
You're legs broken, but you walk.
Some ribs broken, but you're breathing.
You're wooden, but you're acting.
It won't take long.
Just want to verify what we already know.
Cubs suck.
This kid Mark sure wasn't your fault.
The kids cut in on you.
Probably hopped up, they got records.
Want to get high?
Now, this is for the Tijuana police, you understand?
So there won't be any kickback later.
Like to keep our citizens in the clear.
You've got some influential friends.
That's why you're in San Diego now.
Hmm.
I am?
No, I'm kidding.
You're in a cheap Tijuana hospital.
And where are they?
The kids.
And both boys were killed instantly.
But like I said, they're on fault.
Yeah, they're headed to hell.
The four of you are thrown clear.
They found you scattered all over that hill.
The odd thing about the girl, we've been looking for her.
Escaped from juvenile hall last Friday night.
Might not have caught up with her except for this.
She and the kid who was driving registered his man and wife in a motel in Tijuana.
Then they got jumpy.
Made a deal with the other boys, stole her car and tried to make it to Mexicali.
That's when they bumped into you.
Do you have another face you could wear?
They?
Yeah, the three of them in the stolen car.
And how do you know all that?
She gave the whole story to the Tijuana police.
Just before she died.
Yes, sweet.
Yes, yes.
She's dead too.
Didn't I say that?
All three kids in the other car?
We're the convenient precinct.
God.
I know how you feel.
Maybe it's a mistake to feel sorry for kids like that.
But then maybe it's a mistake not to.
Shall I send it in your wife?
Oh, and by the way, we went in and cleaned up your house and you were elected senator
and the girl cast a deciding vote right before she died.
Yes.
It could wait?
No.
Well, once more, end of the breach.
It's time we had to talk.
We haven't talked together for too long.
Really? We hit it off.
Whatever you say, Mr. Stratton.
I'll send her in.
I'm strangely unaffected by all this.
Ow.
Ow!
One ring can rule them all and in the darkness bind them.
And when in Universal City, ride the kitten with the whip ride.
And climb into the 50-foot Ann-Margret.
Why wasn't there more Doodles Weaver in this movie?
Doodles, Doodles, Doodles, Doodles.
Hee hee!
Okay, Mike. We're all set up.
Why don't you start out with a shattering blow to the rib cage?
Okay, all right. Give me some.
Okay, okay. Now the bridge of the nose.
Yeah, the knuckles.
No, no, the back of the knees. Back of the knees.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And remember, it's not mean because he's just a pinata.
You're absolutely right.
Now, run the storm, Mike.
Yeah, give me some.
Give me some.
Come on.
Yeah.
Boy, he gave me some. All right, well, let's read this letter here. This is a nice letter from Mike Blakely.
Hi, Mike.
And Mike Blakely. Put that on the steel store there, will you, Cambot?
Oh, I'm out of breath from giving them something.
And it says, "Dear Mike, Crow, and Gypsy."
And you can see Gypsy is misspelled.
Tom Servo and Cambot.
"I'm seven years old."
Years is misspelled.
"And I love your show."
And love and yer are misspelled.
Oh, that's adorable.
"I watch it every day."
Watch is misspelled.
"My favorite guy is Crow."
That's misspelled.
"I wish he could come and live with me."
This is a fake letter.
Stop playing with me fake letters.
Give me some.
Come on.
You got a little cute picture for me?
Give me that too.
Mike, get a hold of yourself.
It could be a real kid, Mike.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
Still, it might not be.
Give me some.
Frank, what have you got to say for not stopping them from turning me into a pinata?
I'm sorry?
I accept your apology.
And yet, it's not enough.
Are you gonna hit me?
No, I'm not going to hit you.
I've invited a gaggle of candy-starved five-year-olds with Louisville Sluggers.
Boy, are they excited.
Five-year-olds?
Well, that sounds really sweet.
There you go, kids.
Ow!